Office of Educational Affairs, School of Medicine Records UA146
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Mary Y. Lee's files, 1968 -- 2007; UA146.004; 8.4 Linear Feet
  - Graduate Programs in Public Health Accreditation, 2002; UA146.004.035.00007 (Box 35)
  - Graduate Programs in Public Health Accreditation, 2002; UA146.004.035.00008 (Box 35)
  - Master of Science in Pain Research, Education and Policy Annual Report, 2001 -- 2002; UA146.004.035.00009 (Box 35)
    Folder 1 of 3
  - Master of Science in Pain Research, Education and Policy Annual Report, 2001 -- 2002; UA146.004.035.00010 (Box 35)
    Folder 2 of 3
  - Master of Science in Pain Research, Education and Policy Annual Report, 2001 -- 2002; UA146.004.035.00011 (Box 35)
    Folder 3 of 3
  - Master of Science in Pain Research, Education and Policy Interim Grad Program Review, 2003; UA146.004.035.00012 (Box 35)
  - Graduate Programs in Public Health Accreditation, 2002; UA146.004.035.00013 (Box 35)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center-Floating Hospital for Children Research Day Abstract Book, 2002; UA146.004.035.00014 (Box 35)
  - Tufts Employee Skills Development Series, Taking Charge of Your Time, 2002; UA146.004.035.00015 (Box 35)
  - Fall Semester Medical Student Director, 2002; UA146.004.035.00016 (Box 35)
  - Tufts School of Medicine Guide to Third Year, 2006 -- 2007; UA146.004.035.00017 (Box 35)
  - Baystate Medical Center, 3rd Year Medical Student Clerkship Catalog, 2005; UA146.004.035.00018 (Box 35)
  - Tufts School of Medicine Bulletin, 1993 -- 1995; UA146.004.035.00019 (Box 35)
  - Tufts School of Medicine Bulletin, 1995 -- 1997; UA146.004.035.00020 (Box 35)
  - Tufts School of Medicine Bulletin, 1997 -- 1999; UA146.004.035.00021 (Box 35)
  - Tufts School of Medicine Bulletin, 1999 -- 2001; UA146.004.035.00022 (Box 35)
  - Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences Bulletin, 1996 -- 1997; UA146.004.035.00023 (Box 35)
  - Tufts School of Medicine Bulletins, Assorted., 1999 -- 2001; UA146.004.035.00024 (Box 35)
  - Strategic Plan for Scholarship, 2005; UA146.004.035.00025 (Box 35)
  - Tufts School of Medicine Affiliated Residency Programs in Internal Medicine, 1993 -- 2005; UA146.004.035.00026 (Box 35)
  - Stearns Professorship in Health Management, 1993 -- 2005; UA146.004.035.00027 (Box 35)